Abhishek Agri

Samta, laxmipura, Gujarat • 7874816180 • abhishekagri123@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/abhishek-agri-la4016251

The Professional Summary section of your resume is a place for you to write a narrative or summary of your relevant professional experience, skills, and accomplishments. Think of your Professional Summary as a teaser for the employer to read the rest of your resume. Remember to use well known companies or products and numbers when possible.

- · Get clear on audience.
- · Outline what information you want to include.
- · Years of experience.
- · Notable industries or companies.
- · Core skills & keywords.
- 1-2 notable accomplishments.
- Use first person and make sure your first sentence hooks the reader in.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Zonedout Media • Vadodara • Full-time • 07/2023 - Present

Welcome to the exciting world of Brand Strategy, Brand design, and Marketing communications. We are a 360 degree Brand consultancy company based in Vadodara, Gujarat. Where real is now virtual, we strive you create your business into a Brand where it activates, engage, and, evolve across all the channels. We work passionately to let your brand tell stories through designs. As we consistently attempt to cover the latest trends and help our clients elevate, we aim to be the top choice for all businesses and grow together.

Client Service Executive

Patterns Staffing • Vadodara • Full-time • 12/2022 - 06/2023

Patterns is Elevating Excellence as a Leading Force in the Business Process Outsourcing Industry. At the heart of our mission lies an unwavering commitment to excellence. With years of experience as our foundation, we deliver unmatched value to our clients. Quality is our signature, and we gauge our success through rigorous measures: quality, cost-effectiveness, on-time delivery, and innovation. Our secret weapon is our embrace of cutting-edge technology, enabling us to lead in a rapidly evolving landscape. Combined with our forward-thinking approach and unyielding dedication, it propels us towards triumph. We see challenges as opportunities and every endeavor as a stepping stone towards realizing our mission and surpassing expectations. Our services encompass Graphic Design, Vector Artistry, Digital Image Enhancement, Data Processing, Virtual Assistance, Website Development, Staffing & Recruitment, and more. We are your comprehensive outsourcing partner, catering to a wide range of industries, both small and large.

US Healthcare Recruiter

EDUCATION

Graduate in Business Administration

MS University • Vadodara • GPA: 7 • 01/2021 - 12/2023

I am eager to join your esteemed firm, drawn by its reputation for excellence and innovation. I am confident that my skills and align seamlessly with the values and goals of your organization. My proven track record in [mention relevant achievements or experiences] reflects my commitment to delivering high-quality results. I am excited about the opportunity to contribute my expertise, collaborate with a talented team, and further contribute to the success of your firm. I look forward to the possibility of becoming a valuable member of your team.

PROJECTS

Courtyard project

Zonedout Media • 04/2023 - 10/2023

Had a Great experiences.

INTERESTS

Swimming: Cooking, Meeting New people